[Music]
[音乐]
now usa or the family is starting
现在美国或家庭开始
whiskies engineering where do you eat in
威士忌工程，你在哪里吃饭
Carey's engineering seats are immovable
凯里的工程座椅不可移动
engineering know just rainer klausmann
工程知道只是莱纳克劳斯曼
Now my name is motto mine
现在我叫座右铭
name is bond films a yes developer
名字是邦德电影，是的。
network engineer is a lifestyle of
网络工程师是一种生活方式
eccentric builds for years now star of
多年以来的古怪建造
engineering because of so implemented
工程如此实施
lars many many mystery and patterns mike
lars许多谜团和模式迈克
read write from baxter user circuit
百特用户电路的读写
breaker a roll on ice cool stuff but
断路器在冰凉的东西上滚，但
not able to cheer trailrunning in
无法为越野跑加油
production and for example fallback boss
生产和后备老板
boss roger surprise to implement a case
罗杰老板大惊小怪
Brand Case Michael Forsting alright like
品牌案例Michael Forsting还不错，
how startup is using is very jump
启动使用的方式非常快
nice okay you as well famous talks of
好的，您好，还有著名的演讲
jackass star from inception good 1 very
从最初的公驴明星好1非常
easy ear and so far together judith
易听，至今为止朱迪思
place in the world and production of
在世界上的位置和生产
course i am doing a pretty good job
当然我做得很好
Like how canon gold production like
就像佳能的黄金产量怎么样
have tried countless unit tests just too
也尝试过无数单元测试
test but components most of the time
测试但大部分时间都是组件
now never happy fits testing and
现在永远不快乐适合测试和
impotent an ogh it is this output
无能为力的是这个输出
appsfire and top of that we're doing
appsfire，最重要的是，我们正在做的
integration tests and check-in
集成测试和签入
Components swing up correctly
组件正确摆动
and yes, dealing with the pirate bay
是的，处理海盗湾
lighting when you need is because of them
因为需要它们，所以在需要时照明
are you able to implement events on
您是否可以在
very easy and also very zverev are
非常简单，也非常zverev是
the same tests which staples little
相同的测试，订书钉很少
bit more money more time to the end and
多花些钱，有更多时间结束
of course the jobs are sams
当然，工作是简陋的
peschl company is doing so hollow
peschl公司实在太空心了
department casting 15 people dead people
部门铸造15人死亡
what ever i do it
我做过什么
now that's gonna happen maybe we have
现在会发生，也许我们有
This is a box
这是一个盒子
a quality label to release up and
要发布的质量标签，
running in production us-author charity
在生产中运行-作者慈善
percent of politicians are tough politicians
百分之百的政客是强硬的政客
is it coverage hot rod vacation testing
是否覆盖热棒假期测试
writing test on-site tests as well as helper
编写测试现场测试以及帮助程序
sourcecode implementation and now the
源代码实现，现在
setting up mutant is a fragrance and
设置突变体是一种香气，
implementation and what could be the
实施以及可能是什么
worst case last test knew how
最坏的情况是最后一次测试知道如何
green because we are change
绿色，因为我们正在改变
implementation what is it is austin
实施什么是奥斯丁
green
绿
So sat worst case is many babies
所以坐在最坏的情况是很多婴儿
and production a very many many
和生产很多
questions and our heads for example of
问题和我们的头脑，例如
implement together read vorbeck immediately
立即实施一起阅读vorbeck
easier you in reindeer 3 and in this
在驯鹿3中更容易
Instance like yes dettingen a cache
像yes这样的实例将缓存
results with what ever patrolled
巡逻的结果
Time training in a complete set up
完整的时间训练
system and latency i hate latency
系统和延迟我讨厌延迟
normali yes you but him pipelines
师父，是的，但你是他的管道
Rankings education system is one
排名教育制度是其中之一
santisteban horst so well the container
桑蒂斯特班霍斯特集装箱好
cent
一分钱
Start in container since the attacks
攻击以来从容器开始
interaction between them and the snow
他们和雪之间的互动
let it be cool running and just one
让它运行很酷，只有一个
he wanted simple host europe network and
他想要简单的东道主欧洲网络，
was a router switches and of course we
是路由器交换机，当然我们
have to see what happened when you're
不得不看看当你
strange system center service is
奇怪的系统中心服务是
breaking down for example ldp file
分解例如ldp文件
storage whatever and publication will
储存任何内容和出版物
directly it is cars using a kind of
直接是汽车使用一种
services calorie burning bridges okay
服务卡路里燃烧的桥梁还可以
lewis training suspended shift for use
刘易斯训练暂停使用
jurica from netflix service discovery
来自netflix服务发现的jurica
okay as hp service discovery for
可以作为hp服务发现
example jurica vranjes how instanzen yes
示例jurica vranjes如何实例化是
although the same replicator teenager in
虽然在同一复制者少年
gettenau is on the service bus
格tenau在服务巴士上
using small time loadbalancer likely be
使用小的时间负载均衡器可能是
ok where is using with interesting ones
好的，正在和有趣的人一起使用
spring magic i finally we have to save
Spring 的魔力，我终于要救了
our nature still in the data base
我们的本性仍然存在于数据库中
just how pleasing she is with space data
她对太空数据的满意度如何
base in Maryland is best fine
马里兰的基地最好
in a yard estate ag cwi okay so
在一个院子里，农业公司，好吧，所以
we love to help where help big
我们很乐意在帮助大的地方提供帮助
problem is solved a little gold
问题解决了一点金
production of many times new production
多次生产新产品
a national hockey league on his
全国曲棍球联盟
continent insurance company and we have
大陆保险公司，我们有
only to release the summertime
只释放夏季
as much to do on the way as before
像以前一样要做很多
the production flows from just to
生产从正好流向
they are here
他们在这里
Berlin
柏林
Production and production is nice
生产和生产都不错
place and maybe baby contacts
可能还有婴儿接触
heating water day already very components
取水日已经非常重要
tokio application hosting server server
东京应用程序托管服务器服务器
runnings coming up and i would run many
即将到来，我会跑很多
exceptions human resources france
法国人力资源例外
instance afonso network user blackstone
实例afonso网络用户blackstone
enya is still that his place if necessary
必要时，恩雅仍然是他的家
de la rosa cycle of death had
德拉罗莎的死亡循环
however in the un feature here to
但是在这里的联合国功能
products that something i went wrong
我错了的产品
application häßler application baby
应用häßler应用婴儿
exactly half of the stations live to take
恰好有一半的车站可供乘坐
a walk in logfiles technologies
散步日志文件技术
Monitoring tools whatever and special
监控工具无所不包
cases your mallorca prices and increased
情况下您的马洛卡价格上涨
Construction of the story has the post mortem
故事建设有事后验尸
analyzers not about the patients
分析仪与患者无关
are the so welper okay so this
是那么的温柔吗
on distributed computing
在分布式计算上
you can almost see many of them here
你几乎可以在这里看到很多
networks is now reliable as a running
网络现在可以可靠地运行
very good communications network
很好的通讯网络
luther no band firewalls exchange for
路德无带防火墙交换
whatever meadows seen some other parts of
不论草地看到了其他什么地方
the next by leighton size zero the
接下来是leighton大小为零的
fourth velop in locally and the lawyer
本地的第四人和律师
in apolda container things i know you
在阿波达容器中，我认识你
have to be a stranger to what
必须对什么陌生
ever and janus latency we have many
和janus延迟，我们有很多
house installation network
房屋安装网络
the firewall rules have many many klo
防火墙规则有很多很多
sports july so much is latency
七月运动如此之多是延迟
coming up bendriss is infinity ward
即将来临的本德里斯是无限病房
Insurance company is famous for building
保险公司以建筑闻名
patch application recovers day 1 patch
补丁程序恢复第一天补丁
applications or jobs are running for
正在运行的应用程序或作业
our most of the major wars at once and
我们大部分的主要战争
running to working but because they are
跑去工作，但是因为他们
very body and sale in the trees
树木非常有卖
Consumption in the band for the internet
乐队的互联网消费
world at host europe network is for
欧洲主机网络的世界是为了
most of the time to secure the
大多数时候可以确保
cosmic sports bfm is it on
宇宙体育bfm是它
Configuration updates b have some nice
配置更新b有一些不错的
edmonds yes then configuration as well as have
edmonds是的，那么配置以及
to admit that means the battle operation
承认这意味着战斗行动
so you're getting firewall
所以你要防火墙
activated by first and second source
由第一来源和第二来源激活
technologies and change router can
技术和变更路由器可以
want to regret be replaced know how
想后悔被替换知道如何
Replays from established but a very
重播已建立但非常
little components and the moving overtime
小零件和加班
my favorite csu never wanna et mettmanns
我最喜欢的CSU Never Wanna et Mettmanns
you have to cooperate with mad men
你必须和疯子合作
very close to the sea the break from apple
离海边很近
in micron project for advanced company
先进公司的微米项目
either build this glove before glove
要么先戴上手套
paz 1 and would like to spin up new
帕斯1号，并想发展新的
will understand that the good room
会明白，好的房间
in changwon so network whatever the way
在昌原，所以无论如何
we have been allowed to bring cup in
我们被允许带杯进来
just like you interfax is breathing
就像您的Interfax呼吸一样
an external and men and external
一个外部和男人与外部
Advanstar doing so job in a NASA
Advanstar在NASA从事这项工作
Internal lemonheads did not read like that
内部柠檬头不是那样的
twenty years as well as internal there are
以及内部的二十年
is external lettmann a so but
是外部莱特曼这样，但
atmane has lost is delight and so horst
atmane迷失了喜悦和恐惧
account wars disabled foreword proven
帐户大战禁用前言已证明
so, so go with little begging
所以，所以很少乞求
she internally and externally admins transport
她在内部和外部管理运输
costa zero day we have to pay per page
哥斯达黎加零日我们必须为每页支付
of action using the availability
使用可用性进行操作
establish components so first bill is
建立组件，因此第一份帐单是
most beautiful picture of the established
成立的最美丽的图画
said Tschentscher application stack
Tschentscher应用程序栈
yes yes so nice word is office
是的是一个很好的词是办公室
System very anonymous components a very
系统非常匿名的组件
the speechtek is office system
Speechtek是办公系统
implements aim implementation
实施目标实施
stop system again running linux so much
停止系统再次运行linux
by tcp ip implementation some of us are
通过tcp ip实现，我们中的一些人
for whatever giant microsoft windows
适用于任何大型Microsoft Windows
servers are a differentiated one
服务器是与众不同的
svp implementation and if you are
svp实施，如果您是
running for cluster obedience kastrati
运行集群服从性
implements ifpi stack to do
实现ifpi堆栈来做
to do it trends to passivity
做它趋向被动
correctly satisfied
正确满意
sorry for little bit of bashing okay
对不起，扑扑好一点
still the list is the top-ten
仍然是前十名
ecommerce platform sin in germany of
德国的电子商务平台sin
course amazon the sunday-partie
当然，亚马逊，周日派对
allstars island is last youth very
全明星岛非常年轻
Bronson outfit so you will have lost
布朗森的衣服，所以你会迷路
about our sources of the board 5000 us
关于我们的董事会资源5000我们
you just about every second
你几乎每一秒钟
constant turnover incoming via running
通过运行获得恒定的营业额
on the x-series logistics marketing
在x系列物流营销上
campaign for little bit more coming and
争取更多的运动
of course you can use it so much is all
当然，您可以使用很多
about that s all about to be able to
关于那一切都将能够
time with something is broken down the
时间与事情分解了
system but customer it still silently
系统，但客户仍然默默
to be able to bring you when
能够带你去
you tube laser or whatever works
你管激光或任何有效的方法
Disney's architect shot who have the
迪士尼的建筑师拍摄了
implement that architect so defensively you
如此防御地实施您的架构师
bring down the cloud
降低云
local and communication gateway services
本地和通信网关服务
gateway services are coming here
网关服务即将到来
communicator back onto the services
传播者回到服务上
connected to and of course we have been
连接到，当然我们已经
a piece of discovery and service cover
一份发现和服务封面
to the applications to the state of the
到应用程序的状态
Instance lux nice but now looks like it
实例勒克斯不错，但现在看起来像
some things are loud police
有些事很吵闹
in wanning
在万宁
somebody has done that change in the
有人做了改变
Configuration is never so great
配置从未如此出色
able gateway instance service is kari
能够执行的网关实例服务是kari
is up and running yes but i can not wait
已经启动并运行，但是我等不及了
to the state of things is still so nice
到现在的状态还是很好
but you would like to know what this
但是你想知道这是什么
case engineering so let's get started
案例工程，让我们开始吧
what is engineering news is very yes and
什么是工程新闻，是的，
The cables had vibrant chaos there
电缆在那里充满了混乱
or server out of the window whatever
或服务器不在窗口之内
you please do not just for fun to black
你不只是为了娱乐而变黑
He still doesnt wings that there
他仍然不在那里
what i do it for netflix foot use case
我为netflix脚用例做什么
some nobody okay you in obertheres
有些人没事，你好吗
mark is already explained that netflix
标记已经被解释为netflix
started to go to establish
开始去建立
very close and data centers and i
和数据中心非常近，我
have done architect the architect change
已经完成了架构师变更
to in microsoft word fall the twins
在微软词落双胞胎
go to dance and developer go
去跳舞，去开发商
applications am good application java
应用程序很好Java应用程序
python whatever the appointment from many
python无论有多少约会
many thousands of notes officer
数以千计的便笺人员
is a nobody knows wise word granted
是没有人知道明智的话
So the smoky has to kill me is you
所以烟熏杀了我的就是你
Instanzen and the city means so
Instanzen和城市意味着
developers to implement brazil
开发人员实施巴西
pattern into the application so much
模式到应用程序中
have to implement fire change have to
必须实施换火
have to control the time together
必须一起控制时间
service do you have so pastiors makino
服务，你有这么牧师马基诺
system in army
陆军系统
seminar very many many that monkeys
研讨会很多很多猴子
insituform immediately from the network fix for
立即从网络修复程序中获取
example of course the first one stop
当然第一站的例子
Agency monkey monkey wants in jacksons
机构猴子猴子想在杰克逊
the island communication and final
岛上交流与决赛
endboss you out chaos kongos kong is
endboss你出去混乱kongos kong是
to kill you later the streets
以后在街上杀死你
netflix tobias british in mainz he
netflix tobias英国人在美因茨他
yourself to
自己去
is an eps between and please
是介于之间的eps，请
do not start director production of
不要开始导演制作
course we have to do it later in
当然，我们必须稍后再做
production corp initial communication is
生产公司最初的沟通是
our customers and we need some requests
我们的客户，我们需要一些要求
into the system
进入系统
the costa finding ways to use our
哥斯达黎加找到使用我们的方法
education that we expected to find
我们期望找到的教育
buttons put hitherto has blystad
迄今为止放置的按钮具有blystad
inner stage on environment which is
环境的内部阶段
quite similar to production max absolute
与绝对最大产量非常相似
innocence development stage so far
迄今为止的纯真发展阶段
completely so either in warm and you
完全如此，无论是温暖还是你
need to be sure to you are obedient load
需要确保您服从
Testing on stage and we have to you
在舞台上测试，我们有您
please please do not go home
请不要回家
chaos monkey colexon class and they come
混乱的猴子colexon类，他们来了
to you e-mails a mess is not amused
给您发送电子邮件不会惹得一团糟
At the heart of the market, this built culture
在市场的中心，这种固有的文化
mindset story about it
关于它的心态故事
it is bob lux location is rest is on
它是鲍勃勒克斯位置休息
happy because the web is possible
快乐，因为网络是可能的
for service service level response very
对于服务服务水平的响应非常
slowly insam special cases know when
慢慢的insam特殊情况知道什么时候
response from the navi quest before you will
导航操作之前的响应
never response service is north london
永不响应的服务是北伦敦
services colt bob service this box
服务柯尔特鲍勃服务此框
team mates motto not very happy into mo
队友座右铭不是很高兴成莫
ca sinking bad sachsa have to decide to
大约下沉的萨克萨州必须决定
bed response soul agency cia corning bob
床反应灵魂机构cia康宁鲍勃
service and what the plague of the
服务以及什么的困扰
Performance of mining and yet nobody
采矿表现，但没人
kers weather service said customers like you
kers气象服务部门表示喜欢您的客户
in the beta world as implemented ob
在Beta世界中，已实现ob
nobody thinks jositsch is like social and
没有人认为jositsch就像社交和
talk to share about that
谈论分享
servicecenter makes from roundup there
服务中心从那里汇总
any league west papua in front of its
西甲联赛前的任何联盟
many as of fame factory store händelhauses
许多知名的工厂商店händelhauses
author jesse stone just one of four
作者杰西·斯通（Jesse Stone）只是四分之一
points cars and is not to do something
指向汽车而不是做某事
point in the future applications and
指出未来的应用
respond to share resorts and to work
回应度假胜地和工作
together at the beta systems cisco
一起在beta系统cisco
systems engineering it simple first
系统工程首先简单
free ebook download offers have any
免费电子书下载优惠有
questions procedure pin ups after hennig
亨尼格问问题程序针
westens in augsburg e book vom vom
奥格斯堡威斯汀电子书vom vom
netflix something witty at casey rosenthal
netflix凯西·罗森塔尔风趣的东西
one of the founders engineering with
其中一位创始人工程
netflix reinhard end innovation- and
netflix reinhard最终创新
put cars in the casting and without
将汽车放入铸件中
plan
平
mister executive engine which is quite
先生执行引擎，这是相当
like you can read about the pages
就像你可以阅读有关页面
forgot tv trigger otherwise
否则会忘记电视触发
would buddy start to sink ok yes never does
伙伴会开始沉没，是的，永远不会
first impression not like to the conference
第一印象不喜欢会议
you are one and content production
你是一个和内容生产
so you can use and other statements that
因此您可以使用和其他声明
to production to do some load testing
去生产做一些负载测试
shadow traffic proxy in front of
前面的影子流量代理
the rest of the collection
其余的收藏
system engineer test stato loud test
系统工程师测试stato大声测试
of cars engineering education your in
汽车工程教育专业
six levels and first man on course
六个级别，第一人称视角
is in hidden advertising in crises
在危机中隐藏广告
securemail consumption do something that
使用securemail可以做一些事情
works agency package job publication
工务局一揽子工作出版物
He was first off as a platform
他最初是一个平台
level where you can do something is it
你可以做某事的水平
over the cluster in cloud foundry
在Cloud Foundry中的集群上
whatever it takes over the cloud
无论它接管了云
provider services application stack
提供者服务应用程序堆栈
value place checks in latency all you can
尽最大可能检查延迟
eat kaindorf exception I say that
吃kaindorf例外，我说
has called is snappy message is endless
所谓的快讯是无止境的
to implement the level out is the
实施升级是
viadrina's experiments together ours
Viadrina的实验与我们一起
top models the bearer gameday game
顶级模特Bearer Gameday游戏
this is the concept of chaos engineering
这是混沌工程的概念
where you put people in one place for
你把人们放在一个地方
example operations you need to business
您需要开展业务的示例操作
unit developer
单位开发商
yes, live here and soja this
是的，住在这里和大 bean
casting architecture 22 beds experiment
铸造建筑22床实验
up for example what will happen service
例如会发生什么服务
is going down as good as hector cuper
和赫克托·库珀一样好
application to take that could i checked
我可以检查的应用程序
in the game time box gameday format
在游戏时间框游戏日格式中
first thing must hypothesis so what
第一件事必须是假设，那么
happened when wiencek latency incisive
发生在wiencek潜伏期敏锐时
Instance how will you make the anger funny
实例如何使愤怒变得有趣
phrases vorbeck is not coming back to as
短语vorbeck不回来了
a result of review is nasa instance jrz
审查的结果是NASA实例jrz
but reporters like blackjack its
但记者喜欢二十一点
starting with small cars radios obedient
从小型汽车收音机开始
politician running in mum's money that
政客用妈妈的钱跑
money application like killing by instance
金钱应用程序，例如被实例杀死
In fact, an emergency system that makes
实际上，
no sense of experimental north fail
没有实验性北方失败的感觉
because we help finding the increase the
因为我们帮助找到增加
used to kill me applications the sector
曾经杀死我的应用领域
latency inso network of what ever
网络中的延迟
changing is builds continuously
变化是不断建立的
now it's time in the minds insider
现在是时候在内心深处
displays is the the state warriors
展示是国家勇士
starting hypothesis so far
到目前为止的起始假设
we like our servers via expecting so
我们通过期望而喜欢我们的服务器
following fallback for example but
例如，在回退之后
experiment wants like change act lady
实验要像变夫人
killer application whatever in running
杀手级应用程序在运行中
at that time again technical
那时再次技术
steady-state to get some insights into
稳态以获取一些见解
this application is still up and
该应用程序仍处于启动状态
running though we have findings with
运行，尽管我们有发现
fix and after work she offered ricky simms
修理后，她提供了棘手的西姆斯
experiment ways to get back to come up
实验方法让自己回来
soja design experiments surface and the
大 bean 设计实验表面及
turning the helper into the gate though
虽然把助手变成了大门
implement like kansas
像堪萨斯州一样实施
it is we can stop then continues to
是我们可以停止然后继续
you already know how to experiment
你已经知道如何实验
do not do it for you learn the same way first
不要这样做，因为您首先要以相同的方式学习
car can not handle station whatever dawns
不管天亮，汽车都无法应付
plan the experiment fix it first one
计划实验先修好
after work checks leads experiment wants
下班后检查导致实验想要
Faithfully bright is normal
忠实明亮是正常的
sócrates to picture it on the new dashboard
可以在新的仪表板上显示它
swiss life science and information on it
瑞士生命科学与信息
know we are looking at you look video wall
知道我们在看着你看视频墙
is the system working correctly is it
系统工作正常吗？
Huge estate koticks planet criticized
巨大的地产科蒂克斯星球受到批评
nominated steady-state steady state
提名稳态稳态
and is a coremetrics would like to
并且是coremetrics希望
use the cycle offs experiment the system
使用循环实验系统
of correctly working for example with
正确工作的例子
netflix coremetrics clicks per minute on
netflix coremetrics每分钟的点击次数
the play button is somebody is click
播放按钮是有人单击
our play button so video it the state
我们的播放按钮，以便将其录制为状态
and his typical male in a 150
和他典型的150岁男性
It connects a thousand video clips it is jobs
它连接了成千上万的视频剪辑
the system of networking correctly the
正确联网的系统
costa herford will be that
哥斯达黎加赫尔福德将是
Information in the big database and
大数据库中的信息和
second commerce as well as salt from system to
从系统到第二次贸易以及盐
the state
国家
if the last example like ecommerce
如果最后一个例子像电子商务
platform either from monday morning at
平台，从星期一早上在
stanic lures built house three
stanic诱饵盖房子三
hundred requests to three hundred
百个请求到三百个
borders she is there lions our changing
边界她在那里我们正在改变的狮子
[Music]
[音乐]
- patrick bishop different is no
-帕特里克主教与众不同
something wrong and systems succeeded
出现问题，系统成功
medias bfs coremetrics just like hard
媒体bfs coremetrics就像硬
the side of experiment wants instead of 5 -
实验侧要而不是5-
after ten 15 minutes suspected yes
十十五分钟后怀疑是
at least in the starting experiment
至少在开始实验中
Instances went wrong because we have to
实例出错了，因为我们必须
cancel six experiments medicos system
取消六项实验医疗系统
is not least eight as well as holding back
至少要八点
the changes our system like the thing
像事物一样改变我们的系统
be in stansted and high school off
待在学校，高中毕业
system campact iso standards state chaos
系统规范ISO标准状态混乱
tools sets early autumn
工具套装初秋
last year running open ssl speed too
去年也运行开放的SSL速度
sexy performance from East to
从东方性感表演
club traffic jams we can do it just
俱乐部交通拥堵，我们可以做到
wants you can not handle me but not quite
希望你不能处理我，但不能完全
some really have to process is running
一些确实必须运行的进程
our system first kilic had hcd in
我们的系统第一个kilic曾在
Australia this tool from linux systems
澳大利亚，此工具来自linux系统
just be able to do some operations
只是能够做一些手术
you can gries in memory consumption and
您可以消耗内存，
your so good to the time out
你这么好超时
suggestive youtube sony warns of th
暗示性YouTube索尼警告
seconds after the thing is back
事情回来后的几秒钟
state suicide control do not traffic
国家自杀控制请勿贩运
control now we are getting a clover note
控制，现在我们收到三叶草音符
one off we can in fact latency and
实际上，我们可以延迟一下
pacific eastern and device volks traffic light
太平洋东部和设备大众交通信号灯
delay and internet zero the half
延迟和互联网归零
default delay from up to hand
默认延迟到手
million plus / minus 2 cm second is so
万加/减2厘米秒是如此
also to protocol
也要协议
we have noticed dion euro network
我们注意到迪翁欧元网络
internet device center of packet loss
互联网设备丢包中心
and develop positively like that
并像这样积极发展
[Music]
[音乐]
also configures a so traffic thusis
还配置了一个流量
pacific i want to be so nice to do in the
太平洋地区，我想做的很好
monkeys superman mostly toolkit taxi
猴子超人主要是工具包出租车
know proxy
认识代理
i am absolutely oxy blog and you can
我绝对是氧气博客，你可以
change the special one time so lets you
更改一次特殊时间，让您
have you been in more than one
你去过不止一个
team and your consumer applications to
团队和您的消费者应用程序
check your application here will not be
检查您的应用程序不会在这里
trade at leightons follows the courts so
利顿的贸易遵循法院的规定，因此
a makeshift implementation spot events at
临时实施现场事​​件
a time out now we would like to see the
现在有一段时间，我们希望看到
action so displays taxi boxee
动作，因此显示出租车票务员
operating system
操作系统
services stoxx eeebox evil insect
服务stoxx eeebox邪恶昆虫
automatic lee latency in the place more accurate
自动回风潜伏时间更准确
knows jacket dougan toolkit pump
知道夹克dougan工具包泵
anybody hears from daddy is a new tool
有人听说爸爸是一个新工具
to together chaos tests in docker
一起在docker中进行混乱测试
environment group meetings in may and go
五月和五月举行的环境小组会议
away to randomly pickup containers to
去随机捡起容器来
kill you can not change act agency in one
杀了你不能改变一个代理机构
Printer container we can do
我们可以做的打印机容器
Collector's Rex Expressions Topix Randomly
收藏家的雷克斯表达式随机地Topix
samson composed cluster in some
参孙组成的集群在一些
other things and you can use
其他的东西，你可以使用
features of traffic control the
交通管制的特点
happening the hottie explain kuhn
发生辣妹解释库恩
monkey partie
猴子派对
michael forsting well put tool though
迈克尔·福斯特虽然放好工具
the same look demo and top set
外观相同的演示和顶级套装
how can use case engineering platform
如何使用案例工程平台
bought like to do it continuously and
购买喜欢连续做，
would like to share euro experiments
想分享欧元实验
mister colexon sum so department
克雷森先生总和部
cent like need to do it in a controlled
像需要在受控状态下进行操作
way so much is my start up gremlins
这么多是我启动gremlins
trading know how sweet access horst
交易知道如何甜蜜的买入
recognize increase the cpu lotse can do
认识到增加cpu lote可以做的
something our networks day is not
我们网络日不是
kills at the monastery st andrews feature
在修道院圣安德鲁斯功能处丧生
comes timeshift feature pay for free
免费提供时移功能
virgin up and running back limited
处女和奔跑受限
in situ can use the sisters of project
就地可以使用项目的姐妹们
cars to do with their way to set up
汽车与他们的设置方式有关
his experiment stewardess kate in Jason
他的实验空姐凯特（Jason）
format you can trust digital polycollege
您可以信任的数字式综合大学的格式
scan work together resources
一起扫描资源
experiment is one
实验是一
Cooperation platform like sony about you
像你这样的索尼合作平台
so could experiment together you can
所以可以一起尝试
skip to the end son so rosy from monkey
跳到最后，儿子从猴子那么红润
of course i can use cases after that
当然，那之后我可以使用案例
want to be part of europe yes
想成为欧洲的一部分
artifact maybe we can do better way to
也许我们可以做更好的方法
change or why not injected startup
变化或为什么不注入启动
time the leaders start up your spring
领导们开始你的 Spring
good from the churches the olb to extend the
从教会的好，奥尔布扩大
glass only manko wants to automatically
玻璃只有曼科想自动
start and risk and application and
启动，风险和应用，以及
running to do something sign spring
跑去做标志 Spring
Good application of the composer Roger
作曲家罗杰的出色应用
waters able to choose kenya application
沃特世能够选择肯尼亚的应用程序
for using notation on add controller
在添加控制器上使用符号
access controller services
访问控制器服务
Roger is able to recognize a great collect
罗杰能够认出一个伟大的收藏家
watch public fair together which
一起观看公共展览会
collins does endpoint protector trials
柯林斯进行终点保护器试验
and with all sorts throw latency it should
并且具有各种抛出延迟
so you can in fact latency and
因此您实际上可以延迟和
application level specification in the
中的应用程序级别规范
wood fair buchanan insect any kind of
木材博览会布坎南昆虫的任何一种
fix you are ready to get out of your glass
修复您准备好摆脱困境
and finally very skeptical if so
最后非常怀疑
it's on the ball is calling the specific
在球上叫特定
endpoints that's a good look
很好看的端点
tells veiel endboss yes
告诉veiel endboss是
and we have to wait to release in memory
我们必须等待释放在内存中
is configured so you can
已配置，因此您可以
home apple man memory before that pacific
那个太平洋之前的家庭苹果人记忆
time continuously now in front of his text
现在在他的文字前持续时间
release of the smart forspeed hessens pingu
推出Smart Forspeed Hessens Pingu
tech data and you can never let you go
科技数据，你永远也不会放手
change it on the fly twelve year in
十二年内即时更改
budapest up and running the way to
布达佩斯并开辟了通往
influence as well as health care of monkey
对猴子的影响和保健
angels protection reduces island in the
天使保护减少了
spring demo now dawning home-eleven
Spring 演示现在黎明在家十一
implemented dörrie stupid gateway
已实施的dörrie愚蠢网关
components exception handling notated
标注的组件异常处理
silence justin rest template
沉默贾斯汀休息模板
to get back and services session server
返回并服务会话服务器
service and hot wheels and of
服务和风火轮和
Course and services are running in the
课程和服务正在
jump good chaos monkey gateway wants to be
跳好混乱的猴子网关想成为
acted on or results in bic bicc product
对bic bicc产品起作用或导致
One would be the liverpool startpage
一种就是利物浦的开始
so let's get started fingers crossed the
让我们开始吧
Judge the sap of a calling
判断呼唤的汁液
startpage evokes island and so offered
起始页唤起孤岛，因此提供
so you got in cologne to see the page
所以你进入科隆来看看页面
and our other products from the system dfb
和我们来自dfb系统的其他产品
post requests to the fashion and
向时尚发布请求并
services market running of change is
服务市场运行的变化是
Configuration on the fly level one's
即时配置
apple request to the specific instance
苹果对特定实例的请求
wants to act in the space agency as well
也想在航天局工作
in jacking latency between five
在五个之间增加延迟
seconds to value based application
价值应用的秒数
gateway bernauer let's check what our
门户bernauer让我们检查一下我们的
passion service wants to be responding
热情的服务想要回应
this back end fashion service station
这个后端时尚服务站
service ag
服务集团
exactly before sensation services approach
就在感觉服务方法之前
correctly loud koller startpage sets
正确响亮的考勒起始集
uses so well last weekend instance so
上周末实例使用得很好
big latency and getting back after five
大延迟，五点后回来
seconds in the duet much better and numbers
二重奏的秒数和数字更好
exchange configuration of kers monkey
kers猴子的交换配置
you were able to sally configuration at
您能够在以下位置进行配置
one time for in this case with which of
在这种情况下一次
latency which is now the activated to
延迟，现在已激活
exceptions core configure any to any
异常核心可任意配置
kind of exception kevin selection
凯文选择的一种例外
the has called this message
已致电此消息
so let's take a look at internet server
让我们来看看互联网服务器
error log as well as can do it man
错误日志，以及可以做到的人
but now comes later
但是现在来晚了
kompon container here station service
kompon集装箱在这里站服务
investigator diesel locomotive
调查员柴油机车
[Music]
[音乐]
but here is the church context
但这是教会的背景
action clauses cacs market share
行动条款cacs市场份额
Okay, so have many steps
好，有很多步骤
fiercely configurator monkey help around
激烈的配置猴子帮助
much controller offers so let's take a
控制器提供了很多，所以让我们来
look at the cross platform to wait to
看跨平台等
design your experiment in jason format
以jason格式设计实验
and you can use many different drivers
您可以使用许多不同的驱动程序
volks traffic light you can user driver for
您可以为用户驾驶的Volks交通灯
cuba nice to support services to count
古巴很乐意支持服务
supports whatever you can do something
支持您可以做的任何事情
scenario it in nature
自然地设想
so in of course is you in course of whiskey
所以你当然是威士忌
first driver computer users to take
第一个驱动程序计算机用户采取
it to configure york as a monkey inside
将约克配置成里面的猴子
it's time for some experiments
是时候进行一些实验了
containers an open container
容器打开的容器
positively shocked and space up and
积极地震惊并扩大空间
preparation target chair experiment
准备目标椅子实验
is would like to see the gateway
想看看网关
component working correctly as one
组件可以正常工作
outing to experience ranger in jacking
郊游体验千斤顶的游侠
latency in the second act exception
第二幕异常中的延迟
verb to hypothesis latency on the
假设潜伏期的动词
bestseller fashion service increase
畅销时尚服务增加
List gates wants to continue to this bond
盖茨希望继续保持这种联系
to pay is second
支付第二
hypothesis station &amp; service exceptions
假设站和服务例外
gateway wants to continue to respond but
网关希望继续响应，但
pale radius is without between the
苍白的半径之间没有
gateway and to fashion and services
通往时尚和服务的门户
that started to the environment
开始到环境
[Music]
[音乐]
finally also seed jason statham would have
最后种子杰森·斯坦森也有
you so you can describe experiment you
你，所以你可以描述实验
can set up title
可以设置标题
jörg sees all access to what
jörg看到了所有访问权限的内容
wants to happen on a runnings
想发生在跑步上
experiment but there is so opened racing
实验，但赛车如此开放
and steady-state services
和稳态服务
able to check the steady state of
能够检查稳定状态
systems is simply folks traffic light cologne ger
系统仅仅是人们的红绿灯科隆
karjoth startpage responses to be
karjoth起始页响应为
comeback in to be taken into the
卷土重来，被带入
so killed for the connection
为连接而被杀死
working and i would like to expect to
工作，我希望
hundred acre tipico after replacement is that
更换后一百英亩的地皮是
Team of the HC heritage was also in the
HC遗产小组也在
Driver part of the cars that were
那辆车的驾驶员部分
waiting from monkey as currently in point
从猴子等到目前
where we constantly say configuration to
我们经常说到
jump good chaos monkey in this case
在这种情况下跳好乱的猴子
level one apple requests to protect the
一级苹果要求保护
latency between ford and second and
福特与第二和
really nice feature is now like
现在非常好的功能就像
automatic rohrbeck and changing the
自动rohrbeck并更改
Behavior of fashion service and after
时尚服务的行为及之后
experiment roll back on the changes can
实验可以回滚所做的更改
for the experiment as a conficker
为了实验而感到困惑
steady-state respect either finding a
稳态方面，要么找到一个
critical load as well
临界负荷
the cost of running out of time is good
时间用完的成本很好
gives exception
给出例外
On some it's an experiment it falls
在某些情况下，这是一个实验
we have findings because the sponsors
我们有发现，因为赞助商
motto knowledge to fiction and behavior
对小说和行为的座右铭知识
in no time out handling
立即处理
next one can do better life cycle and
下一个可以改善生命周期，
now the simple spank the
现在简单的打屁股
spring cloud gateway cousin prince otto
Spring Cloud 网关表弟王子奥托
ok-power-label to design sam lutfi
ok-power-label设计sam lutfi
to use cases of tricks
使用技巧的案例
develops program full bags and the
开发程序满袋和
witch project is back and counting
女巫项目又回来了
remote services that's the experiment
远程服务就是实验
theme now enough rc cars up to sea
现在的主题，足以让遥控车驶向大海
monsters of the experiment money to do
做实验的怪物钱
list of passwords would like to say
密码列表想说
that needs to access token networks
需要访问令牌网络
no chaos here, according to connect
根据connect，这里没有混乱
cheers have chaos
欢呼声一片混乱
OK
行
Anita Big Chaos was a second experiment
Anita Big Chaos是第二个实验
play jack layton
扮演杰克·莱顿
she wants to put it in my organization
她想把它放在我的组织中
pen and public works by colleagues kensy
肯尼斯同事的笔和公共工程
was doing so here as it works
在这里这样做是可行的
steady-state where it exists rainer summarizes
雨水存在的稳态
kersten kitas in freelancers monkey
在自由职业者中的猴子
business networking correctly but let's
商业网络正常，但让我们
take a look at cars 11 is here
看一下汽车11在这里
but experiment but configuration of
但是实验但配置
experiment but let's take a look at the
实验，但让我们看一下
execution so ranger the stage-x fine
执行，所以护林员在阶段X罚款
would be response from remote service and
将是来自远程服务的响应，并且
after what values ​​fallback kay overbeck
什么值后备凯凯
is really good
真的很好
the product list can do better
产品清单可以做得更好
so now I want and am response team or
所以现在我想成为响应小组或
services pacific eschenau fallback acts
服务太平洋埃舍瑙后备法案
okay what you like with the mt product
好的，您对mt产品有何需求
can do it better way to skate instance
可以更好地滑冰实例
is more accurate binninger services
是更准确的binninger服务
coverage of something it falls like
覆盖类似的东西
how livestock she lamented
她如何哀叹牲畜
newry quest renew instance and have
新任务寻求更新实例并拥有
this instance is working poor st
这个实例工作不佳
System experiment is that's operation
系统实验就是操作
sm smith values ​​because of the influence
史密斯价值的影响
in one instance motors winstons for
在一种情况下，马达温斯顿
fashion week and service dos campos
时装周和Dos Campos服务
Now, Erika is holding out though everyone is coming
现在，尽管每个人都来了，Eri​​ka坚持不懈
very quickly and acquisitions to the
非常快地收购
hands questions for your side
向您提出问题
okay okay
好吧好吧
back to container from the kit experiments
从套件实验返回容器
were extreme today and latency open
今天很极端，延迟开放
workgroup space up that's why the find out
这就是为什么要找出工作组空间的原因
what happens if oslo exceptions
如果oslo异常会发生什么
first second okay now teklogix
第一第二好吧现在teklogix
Hauptschule working correct throw
Hauptschule工作正确投掷
critic lno box everything to be ok
评论家lno box一切正常
[Music]
[音乐]
sessions first strike back okay that
会议首先回击好吗
success only too well
成功只是太好了
emoze remote service ok investors
激励远程服务好投资者
remote services remote service is okay
远程服务远程服务还可以
the hesse in places villinger what
黑森在地方villinger什么
happened to open tracing footnotes
碰巧打开追踪脚注
okay tracing using hunter and able to
可以使用Hunter进行追踪并能够
sea ​​communication between all instances
所有实例之间的海上通讯
of the traffic light control zolas request to
的交通信号灯控制zolas请求
load balancing quest from the gateway instance
来自网关实例的负载平衡任务
from the service she exactly recognizes
从她完全认识的服务中
information here from the choir where
合唱团在这里提供的信息
everything is fine as well as gateways calls
一切都很好，还有网关电话
bestseller special service goose bumps
畅销书特别服务鹅bump
services because of the fine that swf you him
服务，因为罚款，瑞士法郎你
self sambeth response www www still
自我回应www www仍然
have all the back so sets the geologist
拥有一切后顾之忧
systray whose name is on ancestry.de
名称在ancestry.de上的系统托盘
services colt fashion service in the
服务中的柯尔特时装服务
first round hassanzadeh exception like that
像这样的第一轮hassanzadeh例外
very red gold and intersex wise
非常红金和两性智慧
fashion circus is correct like ok who
时尚马戏团是正确的，像谁
built to get more insider distributed to
旨在将更多内部人分配给
Need to get to know the recruitment in
需要了解招聘
the system and software is the special
系统和软件是特殊的
case we still get the corner
万一我们仍然走到角落
That's what application brings to itself
这就是应用程序带来的
went well application new exception
进展顺利，应用程序新异常
handling northeimer handling after that
之后处理北北
we've changed now drink loud gateway
我们已经改变了现在喝大声网关
the way beyond time out you circuit
超越超时的方法
breaker provided by his tricks too
他的技巧也提供了断路器
to implement
实施
2 inso surface who like mister skater
2个像先生这样的表面人
system internet to handle the rows like this
系统互联网来处理这样的行
a just in time money making it
及时赚钱
what my first love it really have any
我的初恋真的有什么
questions richardson at twitter per
理查森在推特上的问题
mail whatever shopping the mosel already
邮寄已经购物的东西
is not a user aufstocker container
不是用户aufstocker容器
stalker has klaus michael forsting good
缠扰者有克劳斯·迈克尔·福斯特
44 computer users at the pool requests for
池中有44位计算机用户要求
something stupid is from open source and
愚蠢的事情来自开源
you can use oh yes i have a christians
你可以用哦，是的，我有一个基督徒
[Applause]
[鼓掌]
[Music]
[音乐]